Guide to the St. Thomas More Editorial Project, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
St. Thomas More editorial project, Yale University, records
1958-1994
RU 293
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
16.25
The records consist of materials compiled as part of the St. Thomas More editorial project.
Yale University. Library
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 32-E (YRG 32-E), Records of Yale University Library programs, projects, and committees.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of materials compiled as part of the St. Thomas More editorial project.
Libraries -- Publishing; More, Thomas, Saint, 1478-1535; Yale University. Library
- University Library. St. Thomas More Editorial Project, 1958-1994; Accession 1997-A-025
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2029
  Scope and Contents
  No inventory available.
  - Adams, Barry B., University of North Carolina, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Albert, Agnes, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Allan, James, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen, Judson, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Allen, Michael J.B., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen, Ward, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Allison, A.F., 1958-1962 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Allen, Ward, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - America, The Editor, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - ACLS, travel grant, spring, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ACLS, travel grant application, April-May, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Andrews/John, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bainton, R.H., 1958, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Aston, Trevor, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Avineri, Shlomo, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Barker, Prof. Arthur, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Barth, Robert L., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bates College lecture, February 5, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Baumer, Frank, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Beal, Peter; literary manuscript index, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bender, Jr., Raymond G., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Berger, Harry, May 1966 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Bertagnoni, Marialisa, 1965, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Bevington, David, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Birchenough, Josephine Mrs., 1963 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Black, Rev. J.B., C.S.B., 1959, 1960, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Blackburn-Carpenter, Mrs. G.S., 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Blackwell, Sir Basil, 1959-1964 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Blackwell's, project book purchases, 1958-1961 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Blaim, Arthur, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Blatt, Genevieve, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Bolchazy, Ladislaus J., 1976 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Borroff, Marie, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Borserine, E.G., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Boventer, Hermann, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Boyle, Marjorie O'Rourke, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Bradner, Leicester, 1958-1972 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Brennan, John J.; St. john's, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Brewster, kingman, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Brown, Trevor, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Brugmans, H., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Bühler, Prof. Curt F., 1962 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Bullough, Geoffrey, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Burchfield, R.W., 1963-1977 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Burke, Robert R.; Rockhurt College, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Bush, Douglas, 1958-1971 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Byron, Rev. B.; Collegio Nepomuceno Rome, 1557 location, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Cambridge University library, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Cameron, Prof. K.W.; Trinity College, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Candelaria, Frederick, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Caplan, Harry, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Caponigri, A. Robert, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Carroll, Gerard L., 1959-1977 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Cavanaugh, John R., C.S.B., 1961-1978 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Celestine, Sr. M., 1959-1962 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Chase, Nicholas J., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Chambers, A.B., University of California, English department, October 4, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Fr. A. Chapeau, Answers, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Chauncey, Henry, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Christ, Carol (English department; Burkeley, California), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Christopher, Mrs. Constance, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Clancy, Father S.D., 1966 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Clark, Miss Marion, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Clayton, TS., 1966-1978 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Clowes and Songs, Wm., LTD, September 4, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - College of Arms, 1959-1963 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Collins, Rev. Joseph, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Columbia University Press, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Conference on British studies (parts 1 and 2), 1962-1979 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Conference on British studies, publications committee, 1965-1974 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Conference on British studies, New England conference, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Coogan, Brother Robert, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Coorke, Francis A., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Coopersmith, Jeffrey, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Corpus Christi College, Valencia, 1963-1966 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Crawford, Charles, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Crépin, André, Amiens (France), 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Crinò, Prof. A; Florence, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Crossett, Prof. John, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Cuddy, Rev. John, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Cullinane, J.J.; Rider College, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Dallett, Joseph, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Daly, James, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Damon, Philip, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Davis, Natalie, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Davis, Walt; Notre Dame, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Dean, Leonard, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Dearing, Vinton A., 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Delcourt, Marie, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - DeMolen, Richard L.; Dict. of Tudor and St. Biography, etc..., 1973 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - de Prada, A.V., 1963-1964, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - de Schryver, A.E., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Devereaux, E.J., 1975 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Devitt, John R.; Thomas More Society, Milwaukee, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Derrett, J.D.M. (Oriental law), 1959-1974 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Demier, Dr. A., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Dircks, Richard J.; St. John's, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Dodds, Margaret Lacy, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Doyle, Dr. A.J., Durham library, 1962-1967 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Doyle, Charles C., 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Duke University Press, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Dunham, Prof. W.H., Yale, 1961-1977 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - University of Edinburgh, librarian, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Edmonds, Anne C., 1963 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Edwards, A.S.G., 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Essex County Council, 1963-1976 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Etudes Anglaises, Monod, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Expense account forms, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Eyston, Mary E.; More, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Fagan, Edward, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Firpo, Luigi, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Fish, Stanley E., 1963 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Fisher, Bernard Rev., 1959, 1972, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Fitzherbert, Cuthbert, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Fitzpatrick, James J., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Foord, Dame Bede, 1973, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Fox, Alistair, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Frechette, Roger J., 1978 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Gabrieli, Vittorio; University of Turino, Rome, 1964-1965, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Garside, Charles, 1962-1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Geritz, Albert, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Gerlo, A.; Brussels, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Giamatti, A. Bartlett, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Gibson, Trevor A., 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Godeman, Nancy, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Gogan, Brian, 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Gordon, Walter M., 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Grace, Michael Bro., 1973-1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Graham, Ellen, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Gray, Hanna Holborn, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Gury, Jacques, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Guy, Dr. John, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Haber, Richard H., 1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Hardison, O.B.; More conference, June 19-24, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Hardy, P., Derrett Festschreft, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Harman, Paul F., S.J. (Rev.), August 26, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Harper, George, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Harrier, Richard, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Harris, Paul T., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Haworth, Marcus A. S.J., (Rev.), 1959-1977 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Haupt, paperback, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Hay, Denys, 1965-1978 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Headley, John; recommendations and correspondence, 1968-1976 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Herbrüggen, expenses, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Herbrüggen, H.S., Dr., 1961-1978 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Herbert, Raymond; Thomas More College, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Hecht, Prof. J. Jean, 1962-1977 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Henry, Avril, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Herbrüggen, Hubertus, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Hexter, J.H., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - High, Margaret P., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Higham, Robin, January 17, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Hill, Harry G., 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Hill, Roland, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Hinds, A. Edward, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Holahan, Michael, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Hooker, Richard, 1974-1978 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Hooker and More, March 4, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Hooker and More, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Horacek, Bruce, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Howell, Roger, 1972-1978 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Hudson, Anne, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Hume, Anthea, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Hume, David; Thomas More church, NYC, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Hunter, G.K., 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Huntington, H.E.; library, 1959-1977 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Hutton, James (Cornell), 1965-1974 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Jayne, Prof. Sears, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Johnson, J. Myron, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Jones, Judith, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Jones-Davies, Sorbonne, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Kagan, Donald, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Kapótsy, Prof. Béla, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Kaske, R., 1961 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Kaufman, Linda, January 23, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Ker, N.R., 1958-1976 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Ker, N.R., possible visit, 1968-1973 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Kernan, Al, 1968-1975 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Kerr, Chester B.; Yale press, 1959-1978 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Khanna, Mrs. Lee, 1973-1978 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Kincaid, Arthur, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - King, John N.; Bates College, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Kinney, Arthur, 1970-1978 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Kinsman, Robert; UCLA, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Kirsch, Arthur C., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Konecsni, J., 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Kristeller, P.D., 1958-1978 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Kuttner, Stephen, 1967-1977 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Lambeth Palace library, 1958-1969 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Lardet, M. Pierre, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Larson, Ronald; San Francisco, T.M. Society, March 14, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Lawler, more lectures, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Leech, Clifford, 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Leslie, Frank P., 1964-1967 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Blanc, Roger, January 9, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Blecna, J.M., July 13, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Bond, W.H.; curator Mss. Harvard, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Bosha, Francis J., January 17, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Boulger, Mr. James, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Bowers, Fredson, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Boyden, James W.;Y.W.P., 1964 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Brainerd, Winthrop, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Brawner, James P.; West Virginia University, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Breunig, Father S.D., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Brady, Mrs. Brookner W., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Brewster, admissions committee, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Brickfield, Cyril F., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Brinkley, Robert A. (Tony); recommendation, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Bruckner, D.J.R., 1960 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Burns, Oates, and Washbourne Ltd., 1959 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Byrd, October 28, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Capron, Paul, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Celeste, Sister Mary; Diocesan Sisters College, October 16, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Chapman, John; Yale, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Chapple, John, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Christian, Bill, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Clarkson, Evelyn B., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Colie, R. L., 1961-1968 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Collier's Encyclopedia, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Collins, Robert, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Fr. Donald, F.X. Connolly, C.S.P., 1958-1965 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Crow, John, 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Cummings, L., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Cummings, Peter; recommendation, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Dawson, Dr. Ford; Gulfport, Mississippi, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Deutsche Staatsbibliothek, February 5, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - DeVane, September 26, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - De Vocht, Henry, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Dewell, Michael, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Dick, John; recommendation, March 7, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Dobson, R.B., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Donlan, Paul A. (Rev.), 1965 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Douglas, Richard, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Doyle, Charles, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Driver, Mary, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Duhamel, P. Albert, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Dulwich College, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Duncan, Mrs. Edgar H., 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Dunn, Catherine, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Dupree, Robert, 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - E.P. Dutton and Company Inc., 1959 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Edelen, Georges, 1959, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Edwards, Anthony S.G., 1970 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Elmblad, Johanna M., 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Elwood, W.A.; University of Virginia, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Elton, G.R., 1960-1978 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Erdman, David, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - Estrada, Prof. F. Lopez, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Fantazzi, Charles, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - Farrelly, David; St. Louis University, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - Feldstein, M., September 29, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Ferguson, Sharon, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - Fishbein, Michael, October 18, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - Fleischer, Mrs. E., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Fleischmann, W.B., 1967 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Flint, Paul H.; Tufts University grad. school, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Ford, George H.; Rochester, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Fox, Prof. D.; Grinnell, May 2, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Fracchia, Charles, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Friedman, Simon, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Fuidge, Miss Norah, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - Glee, Mrs. A., 1967 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Geissman, Erwin W., 1959 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Gershman, Carl, 1964, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Gianelli, A.P.; St. Michael's College, Vermont, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - Gibaud, Abbé Henri, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Gibson, Mr. R.W.; Blackwell's, Oxford, 1958-1972 (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Gilmour Academy, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Ginnetti, Daniel A.; recommendations, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - Glasner, L.B., 1961 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Glynn, James, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - Gogan, Brian (Rev.), 1969 (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - Goodall, J.A., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - Gordon, D.J., 1958 (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - Graham, Howard J., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - Grant, Jack; Australia, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Greene, J.J.; New Rochelle, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - Greenblatt, Steve, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - Gresham Hotel, London, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 164)
  - Griffin, Robert D., 1972 (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Gross, Janet S., 1968 (Box 2, Folder 166)
  - Gueguen, John A., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - Hazen, Allen T., 1959 (Box 2, Folder 168)
  - Healy, James T. (Rev.), 1967 (Box 2, Folder 169)
  - Heiserman, A.R., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 170)
  - Heninger, S.K., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - Hennessy, David, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - Hammond, F., 1962-1969 (Box 2, Folder 173)
  - Harbison, E. Harris, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 174)
  - Harder, Kelsie B.; Professor of English, Youngstown University, October 9, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 175)
  - Harding, Davis P., 1961-1975 (Box 2, Folder 176)
  - Harrington, Msgr.; Catholic Youth Encyclopedia, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Hastings, Margaret, 1960-1975 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Hallie, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Marlow, Charles L., 1966 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Marsh, T.N., 1960-1968 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Marshall, Theodore J., (Rev.), 1962 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Martin, Jay, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Mastronunzio, Mrs. A., 1972 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Georges, May, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - McGrath, Lawrence W., 1962 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - McCarthy, Stephen A.; Cornell University Library, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - McCullock, Samuel C., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - McLoughlin, Helen, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - McLuhan, H.M., Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - McMahon, Bernard, (Rev.), 1959 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - McManaway, James A., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Medical wives, Grace, New Haven, 1965, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Menner, books, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Mertner, Prof. Edgar, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Mesnard, Pierre, March 1969 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Meyer, Sam, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Micro-METHODS-East Ardsley, Yorks, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Mooney, Prof. Margaret, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Morales, Justo G., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Morison, Elting, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Morris, Eileen M.V., 1958-1970 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Morrison, Stephen G.; Boston College Law Library, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Morse College, library list, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Mullett, Prof. Charles; University of Wisconsin, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Murphy, Clare M., 1974 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Murray, J.B., 1959-1961 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Myers, Prof. A.R., 1968 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Newell, Virginia, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - New South Wales library, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Nichols, Fred, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Nixon, Howard B.M., 1968 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Notre Dame press, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Nugent, Prof. Elizabeth M., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - O'Connell, Michael; recommendations, 1967, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - O'Dea, Arthur J., 1958, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Ogden, John D. (Pace), 1963 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Olivieri, Signora San Giacomo, 1959, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Osborn, Mr. James M., 1976 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Ossinovsky, Igor N., 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - O'Sullivan, Richard K.C., 1959, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Ottemiller, John, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Oliver, Revilo P., 1959-1963 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Oxford and Cambridge annual dinner, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Pearson, Norman, November 5, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Perry, Darrance, Undated (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Persse, Mrs. J.W., Undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Phelps lecture committee, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Phillips, D.M., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Pincus, Debra; Sarah Lawrence, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Piper, Mr. D.T., National Portrait Gallery (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Plaisted, E.D. (Rev.), O.S.C., 1974 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Pontifical Institute, Toronto, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Mack, Maynard; Prentice Hall series, 1966-1972 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Prentice Hall Anthologies, 1966, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - President's memo, government funds, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Prévost, Dr. André, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Ramsey, Earl, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Random House, Bogert, 1965-1972 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Ranch, Prof. R.W.; Notre Dame, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Raymond, Richard L., 1964 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Read, Jennifer A., 1968 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Ref. librarian, Library of Congress, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Rendall, John, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Reames, Sherry; recommendations, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Reichner, Herbert; rare books, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Reiter, Robert E., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Roberts, Tony; book list, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Roderich, Robert David; Yale, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Rogers, Elizabeth F., October 1961 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Rogers, Elizabeth F., 1961-1973 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Rohsenow, J., 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Rooney, Miriam Theresa, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Rosenbloom, Arthur J., 1958 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Ruff, Mrs. Emma; Hillhouse, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Ryan, Lawrence V., 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - St. Edmund's College, Ware, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - St. John's, correspondence, speakers and commentators, etc..., 1969 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Sawada, P.A., 1962 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Saffady, W.F.; Wayne State, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - St. Mary's College, California, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Salfas, Stan, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Scepter Publisher; Dublin, Ireland, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Schlauch, Mare, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Schmitt, Wayland; Y.W.P., 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Schneider, John O.P.; Aquinas library, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Schroeder, Harry, 1968-1971 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Georgetown Conference, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Abbreviations, More's works and signature check list, circa 1969 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Form of acknowledgements, for publication, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Advisory committee, list of names, Undated (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Ambassador Hotel, Washington D.C., June 9, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Amici Thomas Mori, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Barnes, Robert (on), Undated (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Berdan library sale, Undated (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Bible, books of project abbreviations, Undated (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Bolt, Mann for All Seasons, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Books purchased for project, 1959-1961 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Brewster Inauguration, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Budget, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Budget estimate, 1960-1965 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Budget, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Budget, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Budget, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Committee meeting, October 19, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Budget, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Budget, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Budget, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Budget, Watkins; old materials, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Conan Law, Undated (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Capricorn books, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Catholic Record Society, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - Chelsea Old Church, Undated (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Standard Works (modern) on Classical language, prose and verse, Undated (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Clement, Margaret; print, Undated (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Confutation, Undated (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Errata, confutation, Undated (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Conscience and consciousness, Folger, November 17, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Copyright agreement, U.S. University presses, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Cranevelt letters, notes on, Undated (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - De Vocht, photos of more letters, Undated (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - Dialogue as literary form, Undated (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - Dialogue of comfort, Undated (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Dialogue of comfort, introduction plan for December 1966 (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - Dewal's report on responses translation, Undated (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Eck, letter to More, 1526, 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Editorial committee, October 7, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Editorial committee meeting; November 7, 1959, pre-luncheon, Gibson estimates (Box 3, Folder 140)